(Sheldon:)She sounds exactly like you.
(Amy:)How'd it go with Leonard?
(Penny:)I don't think he'll be making that mistake again.
(Leonard:)- Good.
- So I know this goes without saying...
(Penny:)...but if either of you tell Leonard
you helped me rewrite this paper...
...I'll beat you both
with a bag of oranges.
(Sheldon:)- Okay.
- Understood.
(Penny:)Now, ladies.
We got a B-minus on this paper.
(Penny:)I think if we put our heads together,
on the next one, we could get an A.
(Bernadette:)But we got you a B-minus on purpose
to make it believable.
(Penny:)Believable?
(Penny:)You saying I'm not smart?
(Penny:)- You're smart.
- No, no.
(Penny:)That's better.
(Amy:)I feel like I'm in high school again.
(Bernadette:)Yeah, doing the prom queen's homework
so she'll like us.
(Howard:)I know.
(Amy:)It's finally working.
(Sheldon:)It's Stephen Hawking.
Answer it. I wanna hear.
(Sheldon:)Professor Hawking,
how nice of you to call.
(Stephen Hawking:)Hello. I really enjoyed our game, Dr. Cooper.
- Oh, me too.
- Or should I say, Dr. Loser?
Ha-ha-ha.
(Sheldon:)Yes, congratulations.
You won fair and square.
(Sheldon:)Very impressive, sir.
- Do you like brainteasers?
- Oh, I love brainteasers.
(Stephen Hawking:)What does Sheldon Cooper
and a black hole have in common?
(Stephen Hawking:)They both suck.
Neener-neener.